<resources>
    <!--<string name="app_name">SeoulInOneWay</string>-->
    <string name="app_name">SIO</string>

    <string name="latitude_label">Latitude: %f</string>
    <string name="longitude_label">Longitude: %f</string>
    <string name="no_location_detected">
        No location detected. Make sure location is enabled on the device.
    </string>
    <string name="permission_denied_explanation">
        Permission was denied, but is needed for core functionality.
    </string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">
        Location permission is needed for core functionality
    </string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="info_location_complete">%s시 %s구</string>
    <string name="info_location_searching">위치정보를 찾고 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="info_location_error">위치정보를 찾아올 수 없습니다.</string>

    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyAE1NAmcnJhwG0RQcTV4NXHWV3EOlewGbU</string>
    <string name="info_license">
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5-%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%A0%EB%93%9C-%ED%96%A5%EC%8B%A0%EB%A3%8C-%EC%9D%8C%EC%8B%9D-%EB%86%8D%EB%AF%BC-%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5-%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5-%EC%8A%A4-%ED%86%A8-%EB%AC%B4%EC%97%AD-3466906/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EC%95%84%EB%82%9C%ED%8B%B0-%EC%95%84%EB%82%9C%ED%8B%B0%EB%B6%80%EC%82%B0-%EB%B6%80%EC%82%B0-%EB%A6%AC%EC%A1%B0%ED%8A%B8-%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EB%AF%BC%EA%B5%AD-ananti-3515815/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EB%91%90%ED%86%B5-%EA%B3%A0%ED%86%B5-%EC%95%8C%EC%95%BD-%EC%95%BD%EB%AC%BC-%EC%B9%98%EB%A3%8C-%EC%A0%95%EC%A0%9C-%EB%A7%88%EC%95%BD-%EC%95%BD%EA%B5%AD-%EC%9D%98%ED%95%99-1540220/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EB%B0%94-%EB%8B%B9%EA%B5%AC-%EC%88%98%EC%98%81%EC%9E%A5-%EC%8A%A4-%EB%88%84-%EC%BB%A4-%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%94-%EC%97%94%ED%84%B0%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B8%EB%A8%BC%ED%8A%B8-%EC%9D%8C%EC%A3%BC-601325/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4-%EC%9E%90%EC%97%B0-%EC%A0%95%EC%9B%90-%EA%B3%B5%EC%9B%90-%EB%8B%B4%EC%96%91-%EC%86%8C%EC%87%A0%EC%9B%90-%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD-%EC%A0%84%ED%86%B5-%EC%88%B2-%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84-3241181/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8%EC%9D%B8-%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%A4-%ED%99%94%EC%9E%A5%EC%8B%A4-%EA%B8%B0%ED%98%B8-%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%BD%98-%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EB%93%A4-%EA%B3%B5%EA%B0%9C-%EC%9C%84%EC%83%9D-%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%9C-646935/\n
        https://pixabay.com/ko/%EC%A3%BC%EC%B0%A8-%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8-%EC%B0%A8%EB%9F%89-%ED%8A%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%94%BD-%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C-%EC%A3%BC%EC%B0%A8%EC%9E%A5-%EA%B3%B5%EC%9B%90-825371/\n
        \n
        \n
        icon image\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/good-ware\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/freepik\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/revicon\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/maxim-basinski\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/pixel-perfect\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/vectors-market\n
        https://www.flaticon.com/authors/freepik\n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Retrofit</b>\n
        Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.\n
        \n
        Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n
        You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n
        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n
        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
        distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
        WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
        limitations under the License
        \n
        \n
        <b>gson</b>\n
        Copyright 2008 Google Inc.\n
        \n
        Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\n
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n
        You may obtain a copy of the License at\n
        \n
        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n

        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n
        distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,\n
        WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and\n
        limitations under the License.\n
        \n
        \n
        <b>swipy</b>\n
        The MIT License (MIT)\n
        \n
        Copyright (c) 2015 OrangeGangsters\n
        \n
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
        of this software and associated documentation files (the \"Software\"), to deal
        in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
        to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
        copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
        furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n
        \n
        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
        copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n
        \n
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
        AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
        SOFTWARE.\n\n
        <b>Glide</b>\n
        License for everything not in third_party and not otherwise marked:\n
        \n
        Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.\n
        \n
        Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
        permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n
        \n
        1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
        conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
        \n
        2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
        of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
        provided with the distribution.\n
        \n
        THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. \"AS IS\" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
        WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR
        CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
        CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
        SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
        ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
        NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
        ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
        \n
        The views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the
        authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed
        or implied, of Google, Inc.\n
         ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        License for third_party/disklrucache:\n
        \n
        Copyright 2012 Jake Wharton\n
        Copyright 2011 The Android Open Source Project\n
        \n
        Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n
        You may obtain a copy of the License at\n
        \n
        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n
        \n
        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
        distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
        WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
        limitations under the License.\n
         ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        License for third_party/gif_decoder:\n
        \n
        Copyright (c) 2013 Xcellent Creations, Inc.\n
        \n
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
        a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
        \"Software\"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
        without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
        distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
        permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
        the following conditions:\n
        \n
        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
        included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n
        \n
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
        EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
        MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
        NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
        LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
        OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
        WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n
         ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        License for third_party/gif_encoder/AnimatedGifEncoder.java and
        third_party/gif_encoder/LZWEncoder.java:\n
        \n
        No copyright asserted on the source code of this class. May be used for any
        purpose, however, refer to the Unisys LZW patent for restrictions on use of
        the associated LZWEncoder class. Please forward any corrections to
        kweiner@fmsware.com.\n
        \n
         -----------------------------------------------------------------------------\n
        License for third_party/gif_encoder/NeuQuant.java\n
        \n
        Copyright (c) 1994 Anthony Dekker\n
        \n
        NEUQUANT Neural-Net quantization algorithm by Anthony Dekker, 1994. See
        \"Kohonen neural networks for optimal colour quantization\" in \"Network:
        Computation in Neural Systems\" Vol. 5 (1994) pp 351-367. for a discussion of
        the algorithm.\n
        \n
        Any party obtaining a copy of these files from the author, directly or
        indirectly, is granted, free of charge, a full and unrestricted irrevocable,
        world-wide, paid up, royalty-free, nonexclusive right and license to deal in
        this software and documentation files (the \"Software\"), including without
        limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
        sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons who
        receive copies from any such party to do so, with the only requirement being\n
        that this copyright notice remain intact.\n
    </string>
</resources>